Finding aid to Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe, Albania to Estonia.
IDC Publishers
- Belarus, 6
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Belarus., 16 June 1999; Amnesty International Report 1999.; (POL 10/01/99); B7 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus., 14 June 2000; Amnesty International Report 2000.; (POL 10/01/00); B8 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus., 30 May 2001; Amnesty International Report 2001.; (POL 10/01/01); B9 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus., 28 May 2002; Amnesty International Report 2002.; (POL 10/01/02); B10 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B11 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus., 26 May 2004; Amnesty International Report 2004.; (POL 10/04/04); B12 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B13 (Microfiche 396)
  - News releases, C
    - Belarus: Amnesty International adopts Russian TV journalists as prisoners of conscience., 30 July 1997; (EUR 49/10/97); C1 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belarus: Amnesty International condemns detention of human rights defender., 23 October 1997; (EUR 49/16/97); C2 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belarus: Findings of Human Rights Committee confirm worsening human rights situation., 10 November 1997; (EUR 49/17/97); C3 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belarus: Police should not detain or ill-treat protesters during unofficial presidential elections., 7 May 1999; (EUR 49/09/99); C4 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Opposition members detained - government stamps out dissenting voices., 26 May 1999; (EUR 49/11/99); C5 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Police should not detain or ill-treat peaceful protestors during presidential demonstrations., 19 July 1999; (EUR 49/16/99); C6 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Government crack-down on peaceful opposition., 22 July 1999; (EUR 49/17/99); C7 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Mass arrests in Belarus - newspaper editor prevented from leaving the country., 23 July 1999; (EUR 49/18/99); C8 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: March of freedom - the authorities must guarantee the right to peaceful demonstration., 14 October 1999; (EUR 49/26/99); C9 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: March of Freedom clash should not be used as excuse for government crackdown., 18 October 1999; (EUR 49/28/99); C10 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Amnesty international welcomes release of former Prime Minister., 30 November 1999; (EUR 49/33/99); C11 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Prisoner of Conscience beaten and dragged into Minsk court., 14 December 1999; (EUR 49/34/99); C12 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Council of Europe urged to consider seriously human rights in Belarus., 25 January 2000; (EUR 49/04/00); C13 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Crack down on dissidents continues., 11 February 2000; (EUR 49/05/00); C14 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Crucial week for human rights in Belarus., 13 March 2000; (EUR 49/08/00); C15 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Opposition MP jailed - the price of opposing a President., 17 March 2000; (EUR 49/09/00); C16 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Day of Freedom protest must be free from human rights violations., 23 March 2000; (EUR 49/10/00); C17 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Journalists detained in attempt to silence dissent., 27 March 2000; (EUR 49/11/00); C18 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: former prime minister narrowly escapes return to prison., 19 May 2000; (EUR 49/17/00); C19 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Compensation trial marred by intimidation., 31 May 2000; (EUR 49/19/00); C20 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Dissent and impunity in Belarus., 21 June 2000; (EUR 49/20/00); C21 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Freedom March 2000 - the authorities must avoid repeat of last year's Freedom March crack-down., 28 September 2000; (EUR 49/22/00); C22 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Crack down on young protesters., 13 November 2000; (EUR 49/24/00); C23 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Immediate action needed to end torture., 21 November 2000; (EUR 49/25/00); C24 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Human rights defenders in the spotlight of the state., 8 August 2001; (EUR 49/06/01); C25 (Microfiche 304)
    - Europe: Thousands of disappeared'' await justice., 30 August 2001; (EUR 01/04/01); C26 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus: Right to speak out violated ahead of presidential elections., 5 September 2001; (EUR 49/10/01); C27 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus: More arrests amidst welcome release of prisoner of conscience., 25 March 2002; (EUR 49/05/02); C28 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: Condemned for speaking the truth., 25 June 2002; (EUR 49/12/02); C29 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: People's March'' must not result in violations of people's rights., 10 March 2003; (EUR 49/001/03); C30 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus: Independence Day Marred by New Wave of Detentions., 24 March 2003; (EUR 49/002/03); C31 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus: And then there were none., 29 October 2003; (EUR 49/006/03); C32 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus: Stifling the promotion of human rights., 29 March 2004; (EUR 49/05/04); C33 (Microfiche 371)
    - Establishing the fate of Belarus' disappeared''., 28 April 2004; (EUR 49/10/04); C34 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Stop harassing independent trade unions and their activists., 1 May 2004; (EUR 49/12/04); C35 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: No Freedom of Expression., 10 June 2004; (EUR 49/13/04); C36 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Demonstrators must be allowed freedom of expression., 20 July 2004; (EUR 49/14/04); C37 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: New prisoners of conscience., 22 July 2004; (EUR 49/15/04); C38 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Imprisoned for publishing a poem., 10 September 2004; (EUR 49/17/04); C39 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus/Uzbekistan: The last executioners., 4 October 2004; (EUR 04/06/04); C40 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus/Uzbekistan: The last executioners: Summary., 4 October 2004; (EUR 04/07/04); C41 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Opposition cannot be stifled., 20 October 2004; (EUR 49/21/04); C42 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Action is needed to stop violations of the Right to Freedom of Expression and Association., 15 December 2004; (EUR 49/23/04); C43 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Amnesty International demands fair trial for possible Prisoner of Conscience., 22 December 2004; (EUR 49/24/04); C44 (Microfiche 371)
    - A coalition of non-governmental organizations is calling for a death penalty-free zone in Europe and Central Asia., 20 April 2005; (ACT 50/012/2005); C45 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus: Punished for exercising their right to freedom of expression., 14 June 2005; (EUR 49/007/2005); C46 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus: Prisoner of Conscience Professor Yury Bandazhevsky is free., 12 August 2005; (EUR 49/009/2005); C47 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus: Georgians held as prisoners of conscience as clampdown on opposition continues., 31 August 2005; (EUR 49/010/2005); C48 (Microfiche 396)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Belarus: Former prime minister imprisoned in clampdown on opposition., 1 October 1999; Worldwide Appeals October 1999.; (NWS 22/06/99); D1 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: The cost of opposing the President., 1 November 1999; Amnesty International Newsletter November 1999.; (NWS 21/06/99); D2 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Worldwide Appeals - Opposition Figure Sentenced to Six Years' Imprisonment., 1 November 2000; Amnesty International newsletter November 2000.; (NWS 21/06/00); D3 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Defenders at Risk., 1 May 2001; The Wire May 2001.; (NWS 21/04/01); D4 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus: Worldwide appeals: Anniversary of disappearance''., 1 July 2001; The Wire, July 2001. Vol.31, No.5.; (NWS 21/06/01); D5 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus: One more victim of Chernobyl?, 1 October 2001; The Wire, October 2001. Vol.31, No.7.; (NWS 21/08/01); D6 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus: Worldwide appeals updates: Released in Belarus., 1 May 2002; The Wire, May 2002. Vol. 32, No. 4.; (NWS 21/04/02); D7 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: Police in Belarus stifle peaceful protests., 1 July 2002; The Wire, July 2002. Vol. 32, No. 6.; (NWS 21/06/02); D8 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: Worldwide appeals: Paying the price of opposition., 1 November 2002; The Wire: November 2002. Vol. 32, No. 09.; (NWS 21/09/02); D9 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: Your appeals make a difference: Updates 2002., 1 February 2003; The Wire, February 2003. Vol. 03, No. 1.; (NWS 21/001/03); D10 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus: AI campaigns for trade unionists., 1 May 2004; The Wire: May 2004. Vol. 34, No. 4.; (NWS 21/04/04); D11 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Trade unionists under threat in Belarus., 1 May 2004; The Wire: May 2004. Vol. 34, No. 4.; (NWS 21/04/04); D12 (Microfiche 371)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Republic of Belarus: Retentionist., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E1 (Microfiche 132)
    - Belarus: the death penalty; conscientious objection to military service; ratification of international human rights instruments., 6/1992; Amnesty International concerns in Europe November 1991 - April 1992.; (EUR 01/03/92); E2 (Microfiche 132)
    - Belarus: Death penalty statistics., 6/1992; Death Penalty News June 1992.; (ACT 53/03/92); E3 (Microfiche 132-133)
    - Belarus: the death penalty., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E4 (Microfiche 133)
    - Belarus: Death penalty statistics., 12/1992; Death Penalty News: December 1992.; (ACT 53/05/92); E5 (Microfiche 133)
    - Belarus: Summary of Amnesty International's concerns., 6/1992; (EUR 49/01/92); E6 (Microfiche 133)
    - Belarus: The death penalty; allegations of ill-treatment in prison; ratifications., 1 June 1993; Concerns in Europe November 1992 - April 1993.; (EUR 01/01/93); E7 (Microfiche 149)
    - Belarus: Work for legislative change., 1 January 1994; Violations of the rights of homosexuals: extracts from Amnesty International action materials.; (POL 30/01/94); E8 (Microfiche 166)
    - Belarus: The death penalty; homosexuality; conscientious objection to military service., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E9 (Microfiche 166)
    - Belarus: The death penalty; homosexuality; conscientious objection., 1 June 1994; Concerns in Europe November 1993 - April 1994.; (EUR 01/02/94); E10 (Microfiche 166)
    - Belarus: The death penalty., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E11 (Microfiche 184)
    - Belarus: The death penalty; allegations of ill-treatment; repeal of the law on sodomy., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E12 (Microfiche 184)
    - Republic of Belarus: Igor Mirenkov., 7 September 1995; (EUR 49/05/95); E13 (Microfiche 184)
    - Republic of Belarus: Igor Yurevich Kopytin., 20 November 1995; (EUR 49/08/95); E14 (Microfiche 184)
    - Belarus., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E15 (Microfiche 203)
    - Belarus., 1 August 1996; Concerns in Europe January - June 1996.; (EUR 01/02/96); E16 (Microfiche 204)
    - Belarus., 1 March 1997; Concerns in Europe July - December 1996.; (EUR 01/01/97); E17 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belarus., 15 April 1997; Out of the margins: the right to conscientious objection to military service in Europe.; (EUR 01/02/97); E18 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belarus: Referendum., 1 June 1997; The death penalty worldwide: developments in 1996.; (ACT 50/05/97); E19 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belarus: Further allegations of ill-treatment of peaceful demonstrators by police., 1 September 1997; Concerns in Europe January - June 1997.; (EUR 01/06/97); E20 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belarus: Belarus in front of the UN Human Rights Committee; prisoners of conscience; the death penalty; allegations of torture in death penalty cases; ill-treatment of human rights defender., 1 November 1997; AI Concerns in Europe: July-October 1997 Supplement.; (EUR 01/07/97); E21 (Microfiche 223)
    - Belarus: Belarus in front of the UN Human Rights Committee; prisoners of conscience; further restrictions on freedom of expression; the death penalty., 1 February 1998; Concerns in Europe, July - December 1997.; (EUR 01/01/98); E22 (Microfiche 242)
    - Belarus: Arbitrary arrests, torture and ill-treatment of peaceful demonstrators; prisoners of conscience; severe restrictions on freedom of expression: prisoners of cosncience; the death penalty., 1 September 1998; Concerns in Europe January-June 1998.; (EUR 01/02/98); E23 (Microfiche 242)
    - Belarus: Vera Stremkovskaya - persecution of a human rights lawyer., 30 November 1998; (EUR 49/13/98); E24 (Microfiche 242)
    - Belarus: Torture and ill-treatment of peaceful demonstrators by the police, arbitrary arrests and prisoners of conscience., 30 December 1998; (EUR 49/14/98); E25 (Microfiche 242)
    - Belarus., 1 April 1999; Concerns in Europe July-December 1998.; (EUR 01/01/99); E26 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Prisoner of Conscience: Mikhail Chigir., 15 April 1999; (EUR 49/06/99); E27 (Microfiche 261)
    - Belarus: Torture and Ill-treatment of peaceful demonstrators by the police, arbitrary arrests and prisoners of conscience., 2 July 1999; (EUR 49/12/99); E28 (Microfiche 261-262)
    - Belarus: Arbitrary arrests of peaceful demonstrators, ill-treatment of prisoners, prisoners of conscience., 1 August 1999; Concerns in Europe January - June 1999.; (EUR 01/02/99); E29 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belarus: Vera Stremkovskaya: the continued persecution of a human rights lawyer., 27 September 1999; (EUR 49/05/99); E30 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belarus: Possible prisoners of conscience., 4 October 1999; (EUR 49/24/99); E31 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belarus: Possible prisoner of conscience: Professor Yury Bandazhevsky., 18 October 1999; (EUR 49/27/99); E32 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belarus: Medical lettering writing action: Professor Yury Bandazhevsky., 1 December 1999; (EUR 49/35/99); E33 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belarus: Possible Disappearances'' in Belarus., 1 January 2000; (EUR 49/03/00); E34 (Microfiche 282)
    - Belarus: Further information on medical letter writing action on Professor Yury Bandazhevsky., 18 January 2000; (EUR 49/01/00); E35 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belarus., 1 March 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe July-December 1999.; (EUR 01/01/00); E36 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belarus: Conscientious objector - Valentine Gulai., 28 March 2000; (EUR 49/12/00); E37 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belarus: Imprisonment for punishment of professional critique., 22 May 2000; Harming the healers: Violations of the human rights of health professionals.; (ACT 75/02/00); E38 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belarus: Dissent and impunity., 21 June 2000; (EUR 49/14/00); E39 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belarus., 21 August 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe: January - June 2000.; (EUR 01/03/00); E40 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belarus., 1 March 2001; Concerns in Europe July-December 2000.; (EUR 01/01/01); E41 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus: Briefing for the UN Committee against Torture., 18 April 2001; (EUR 49/02/01); E42 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus: Vera Stremkovskaya, protecting those who protect human rights., 1 May 2001; Amnesty International Annual Review 2000.; (ORG 10/03/01); E43 (Microfiche 304)
    - Belarus: In the spotlight of the State: Human Right Defenders in Belarus., 8 August 2001; (EUR 49/05/01); E44 (Microfiche 304-305)
    - Belarus: Professor Yury Bandazhevsky - Prisoner of Conscience., 22 August 2001; (EUR 49/08/01); E45 (Microfiche 305)
    - Belarus., 1 September 2001; Concerns in Europe January - June 2001.; (EUR 01/03/01); E46 (Microfiche 305)
    - Belarus: Medical letter writing action: Call for the release of medical academic Professor Bandazhevsky., 13 September 2001; (EUR 49/11/01); E47 (Microfiche 305)
    - Belarus: Four years on - Prisoner of Conscience, Andrey Klimov., 27 February 2002; (EUR 49/01/02); E48 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: As long as there are journalists, there will be prison cells''., 7 May 2002; (EUR 49/07/02); E49 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: Trodden underfoot: Peaceful protest in Belarus., 10 May 2002; (EUR 49/08/02); E50 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: Appeals case., 15 May 2002; (EUR 49/09/02); E51 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus., 30 May 2002; Concerns in Europe Bulletin: July - December 2001.; (EUR 01/02/02); E52 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: Without trace: Uncovering the fate of Belarus' Disappeared''., 1 September 2002; (EUR 49/13/02); E53 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus., 1 September 2002; Concerns in Europe January - June 2002.; (EUR 01/07/02); E54 (Microfiche 322)
    - Belarus: Renewed call for medical care and release of medical academic, Professor Bandazhevsky: Medical Action., 2 October 2002; (EUR 49/16/02); E55 (Microfiche 323)
    - Belarus:, 28 May 2003; Good News Stories: January 2002 to April 2003.; (POL 10/004/03); E56 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus: Human rights defenders under pressure in Belarus., 18 September 2003; (EUR 49/004/03); E57 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus., 1 October 2003; Concerns in Europe and Central Asia January - June 2003.; (EUR 01/016/03); E58 (Microfiche 346)
    - Amnesty International's Written Statement to the 2003 OSCE Human Dimensions Implementation Meeting for Working Session 7: The Question of Abolition of Capital Punishment., 7 October 2003; (IOR 52/003/03); E59 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus: Public Appeal. End the silencing of human rights offenders., 6 November 2003; (EUR 49/007/03); E60 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus: MEDICAL ACTION Renewed appeal for medical care and release of medical academic, Professor Yury Bandazhevsky., 17 December 2003; (EUR 49/008/03); E61 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belarus:, 1 January 2004; 2004 UN Commission on Human Rights. Mission: To Promote and Protect Human Rights.; (IOR 41/01/04); E62 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Stifling the promotion of human rights., 29 March 2004; (EUR 49/04/04); E63 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: End the Silencing of Human Rights Defenders. The case of Spring-96 - Public Appeal., 26 April 2004; (EUR 49/08/04); E64 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Arbitrary Detention of Peaceful Demonstrators. The case of Aksana Novikava - Public Appeal., 26 April 2004; (EUR 49/07/04); E65 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Arbitrary detention of trade union activists - Public Appeal., 1 May 2004; (EUR 49/02/04); E66 (Microfiche 371)
    - Belarus: Europe and Central Asia: Concerns in Europe and Central Asia: July - December 2003., 1 May 2004; (EUR 01/01/04); E67 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus: Arbitrary detention of trade union activists. The case of Alyaksandr Yaroshuk - Public Appeal., 1 May 2004; (EUR 49/03/04); E68 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus: End the Silencing of Human Rights Defenders. The case of Legal Assistance to the Population - Public Appeal., 7 May 2004; (EUR 49/11/04); E69 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus: Belarus: Constitutional Court ruling:, 1 June 2004; Death Penalty News June 2004.; (ACT 53/01/04); E70 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus:, 1 September 2004; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region January - June 2004.; (EUR 01/05/04); E71 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus: End the Silencing of Human Rights Defenders: Public appeal: The case of the Belarusian Helsinki Committee., 16 September 2004; (EUR 49/18/04); E72 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus and Uzbekistan: The Last Executioners: The trend towards abolition in the former Soviet space., 4 October 2004; (EUR 04/09/04); E73 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus: Make Europe and Central Asia a Death Penalty - Free Zone! The cases of Sergei Lishchuk and Anton Bondarenko., 4 October 2004; (EUR 49/16/04); E74 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus:, 16 November 2004; Sudan: Arming the perpetrators of grave abuses in Darfur.; (AFR 54/139/04); E75 (Microfiche 372)
    - Belarus: End the Silencing of Human Rights Defenders: The case of the Belarusian Helsinki Committee., 18 November 2004; (EUR 49/22/04); E76 (Microfiche 372)
    - Public Appeal: Deadly Secrets: A Heritage from the Soviet Union., 21 December 2004; (EUR 04/11/04); E77 (Microfiche 373)
    - Belarus: Mikhail Marinich - opposition politician imprisoned for his political beliefs., 8 February 2005; (EUR 49/001/2005); E78 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus., 5 April 2005; The death penalty worldwide: developments in 2004.; (ACT 50/001/2005); E79 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus: Suppressing the last voices of peaceful dissent., 26 April 2005; (EUR 49/004/2005); E80 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus: Chernobyl commemoration ends in large-scale arrests., 29 April 2005; (EUR 49/005/2005); E81 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus: Human rights defenders speakers tour: Profile - Iryna Toustsik., 16 May 2005; (EUR 49/006/2005); E82 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus: Appeal case: Right to freedom of assembly: Prominent opposition activists sentenced., 29 June 2005; (EUR 49/008/2005); E83 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus., 1 September 2005; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: July - December 2004.; (EUR 01/002/2005); E84 (Microfiche 396)
    - Amnesty International's Statements to the 2005 OSCE Human Dimension Implementation Meeting., 20 September 2005; (IOR 30/014/2005); E85 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus., 16 November 2005; Human Rights Defenders in Eurasia.; (EUR 01/014/2005); E86 (Microfiche 396)
    - Belarus., 1 December 2005; Europe Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: January - June 2005.; (EUR 01/012/2005); E87 (Microfiche 396)
- Belgium, 7
  - Publications, A
    - Belgium., 1989; Country survey section of When the State Kills ...'' The Death Penalty v. Human Rights.; (ACT 51/07/89); A1 (Microfiche 96)
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Belgium., 17 June 1998; Amnesty International Report 1998.; (POL 10/01/98); B1 (Microfiche 242)
    - Belgium., 16 June 1999; Amnesty International Report 1999.; (POL 10/01/99); B2 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belgium., 14 June 2000; Amnesty International Report 2000.; (POL 10/01/00); B3 (Microfiche 283)
    - Belgium., 30 May 2001; Amnesty International Report 2001.; (POL 10/01/01); B4 (Microfiche 305)
    - Belgium., 28 May 2002; Amnesty International Report 2002.; (POL 10/01/02); B5 (Microfiche 323)
    - Belgium., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B6 (Microfiche 346)
    - Belgium., 26 May 2004; Amnesty International Report 2004.; (POL 10/04/04); B7 (Microfiche 373)
    - Belgium., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B8 (Microfiche 397)
  - News releases, C
    - Belgium: Media advisory on death of Nigerian asylum-seeker, Semira Adamu: Amnesty International expresses concern to Belgium authorities., 25 September 1998; (EUR 14/01/98); C1 (Microfiche 242)
    - Belgium: Round-up and deportation of Slovak Romani asylum-seekers., 5 October 1999; (EUR 14/02/99); C2 (Microfiche 262)
    - Belgium: Universal jurisdiction., 22 March 2000; (EUR 14/01/00); C3 (Microfiche 283)
    - Rwanda:Belgian court judgment is a great step in the fight against impunity., 8 June 2001; (AFR 47/01/01); C4 (Microfiche 305)
    - Israel and Occupied Territories: Amnesty International urges investigation of Ariel Sharon., 3 October 2001; (MDE 15/89/01); C5 (Microfiche 305)
    - Belgium: Semira Adamu's case an opportunity to further review expulsion procedures., 15 March 2002; (EUR 14/01/02); C6 (Microfiche 323)
    - Israel/Belgium: Dismay at Sharon case decision., 26 June 2002; (MDE 15/101/02); C7 (Microfiche 323)
    - Israel: International justice for Sabra and Chatila victims., 25 September 2002; (MDE 15/144/02); C8 (Microfiche 323)
    - Belgium: The death of Semira Adamu - Responsibilities past and present., 10 December 2003; (EUR 14/005/03); C9 (Microfiche 346)